let mediumadditionquestions = [
    {
        question: "What is 48 + 19",
        AnswerA: "65",
        AnswerB: "66",
        AnswerC: "67",
        AnswerD: "68",
        correctAnswer: "67",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 23 + 57",
        AnswerA: "80",
        AnswerB: "85",
        AnswerC: "90",
        AnswerD: "95",
        correctAnswer: "80",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 13 + 70",
        AnswerA: "81",
        AnswerB: "82",
        AnswerC: "83",
        AnswerD: "84",
        correctAnswer: "83",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 38 + 43",
        AnswerA: "78",
        AnswerB: "79",
        AnswerC: "80",
        AnswerD: "81",
        correctAnswer: "81",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 27 + 36",
        AnswerA: "62",
        AnswerB: "63",
        AnswerC: "64",
        AnswerD: "65",
        correctAnswer: "63",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 65 + 22",
        AnswerA: "86",
        AnswerB: "87",
        AnswerC: "88",
        AnswerD: "89",
        correctAnswer: "87",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 35 + 28",
        AnswerA: "63",
        AnswerB: "64",
        AnswerC: "65",
        AnswerD: "66",
        correctAnswer: "63",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 26 + 48",
        AnswerA: "71",
        AnswerB: "72",
        AnswerC: "73",
        AnswerD: "74",
        correctAnswer: "74",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 69 + 19",
        AnswerA: "86",
        AnswerB: "87",
        AnswerC: "88",
        AnswerD: "89",
        correctAnswer: "88",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 45 + 37",
        AnswerA: "81",
        AnswerB: "82",
        AnswerC: "83",
        AnswerD: "84",
        correctAnswer: "82",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 47 + 27",
        AnswerA: "74",
        AnswerB: "75",
        AnswerC: "76",
        AnswerD: "77",
        correctAnswer: "74",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 35 + 35",
        AnswerA: "65",
        AnswerB: "70",
        AnswerC: "75",
        AnswerD: "80",
        correctAnswer: "70",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 46 + 11",
        AnswerA: "57",
        AnswerB: "58",
        AnswerC: "59",
        AnswerD: "60",
        correctAnswer: "57",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 58 + 17",
        AnswerA: "70",
        AnswerB: "75",
        AnswerC: "80",
        AnswerD: "85",
        correctAnswer: "85",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 61 + 19",
        AnswerA: "70",
        AnswerB: "80",
        AnswerC: "90",
        AnswerD: "100",
        correctAnswer: "80",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 50 + 50",
        AnswerA: "85",
        AnswerB: "90",
        AnswerC: "95",
        AnswerD: "100",
        correctAnswer: "100",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 41 + 41",
        AnswerA: "82",
        AnswerB: "84",
        AnswerC: "86",
        AnswerD: "88",
        correctAnswer: "82",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 77 + 22",
        AnswerA: "96",
        AnswerB: "97",
        AnswerC: "98",
        AnswerD: "99",
        correctAnswer: "99",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 72 + 23",
        AnswerA: "92",
        AnswerB: "93",
        AnswerC: "94",
        AnswerD: "95",
        correctAnswer: "95",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 34 + 24",
        AnswerA: "55",
        AnswerB: "56",
        AnswerC: "57",
        AnswerD: "58",
        correctAnswer: "58",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 93 + 4",
        AnswerA: "96",
        AnswerB: "97",
        AnswerC: "98",
        AnswerD: "99",
        correctAnswer: "97",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 82 + 11",
        AnswerA: "91",
        AnswerB: "92",
        AnswerC: "93",
        AnswerD: "94",
        correctAnswer: "93",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 65 + 18",
        AnswerA: "83",
        AnswerB: "84",
        AnswerC: "85",
        AnswerD: "86",
        correctAnswer: "83",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 47 + 28",
        AnswerA: "72",
        AnswerB: "73",
        AnswerC: "74",
        AnswerD: "75",
        correctAnswer: "75",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 66 + 7",
        AnswerA: "73",
        AnswerB: "74",
        AnswerC: "75",
        AnswerD: "76",
        correctAnswer: "73",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 59 + 22",
        AnswerA: "78",
        AnswerB: "79",
        AnswerC: "80",
        AnswerD: "81",
        correctAnswer: "81",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 33 + 23",
        AnswerA: "50",
        AnswerB: "55",
        AnswerC: "60",
        AnswerD: "65",
        correctAnswer: "55",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 58 + 13",
        AnswerA: "71",
        AnswerB: "72",
        AnswerC: "73",
        AnswerD: "74",
        correctAnswer: "71",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 56 + 21",
        AnswerA: "75",
        AnswerB: "76",
        AnswerC: "77",
        AnswerD: "78",
        correctAnswer: "77",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 51 + 27",
        AnswerA: "75",
        AnswerB: "76",
        AnswerC: "77",
        AnswerD: "78",
        correctAnswer: "78",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 35 + 39",
        AnswerA: "73",
        AnswerB: "74",
        AnswerC: "75",
        AnswerD: "76",
        correctAnswer: "74",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 29 + 25",
        AnswerA: "51",
        AnswerB: "52",
        AnswerC: "53",
        AnswerD: "54",
        correctAnswer: "54",
    },
]